Today I'm going to prove to you that I can through this 15 centimeter wide neck here in this catsuit
Because yes, it is possible and it's not even that hard
But after my last neck entry catsuit video a few weeks ago
I was a bit flabbergasted about all the comments that were like how do you get into it? How do you get out of it?
I can't imagine so I'm going to help you out guys. I have a mission to
educate you a bit and I'm going to get into this and you can watch. Alright I
put something on the floor because normally I do this in my bathroom and I
wear a bodysuit because this is not for the look in the end this is a how to put
a neck entry catsuit on and off so I'm doing this the YouTube safe version.
First make sure it's on the right side so the outside on the outside. Ideally
you washed it before and put latex china in the water so it is already nice and
oily on the inside I'm going to say oily a lot because it's just the word I use
but I usually talk about silicone oil especially for latex so don't just use
any oil but dressing aid and products made for latex okay going to put a bit
on myself and now you have to imagine dressing like with tights you have to
squeeze from top to the bottom into the garment so front side and since it's
latex gorgeous you point to five millimeters really really stretchy so
come on guys this is possible so it's already super slippery on the inside now
I'm starting in my case with the right leg and I'm searching for the side seams
of the leg and make sure they're really on the sides of the leg I'm scrunching up
Now I'm simply putting my foot through it.
Make sure that the side seam is here on the inside and the outside.
And just with the tights pulling it up until approximately right here with the thigh.
And then I'm going to do this with the other leg as well.
It gets easier with time, it's simply a matter of practice.
And to be honest, normally I don't do this alone, I have help because it's easier.
So we'll see how I will do today.
The first tricky part is getting it over the hips.
That was the first step.
Just to remind you, this is the neck that is currently around my waist.
So it's as easy as that.
Of course I do have practice and of course I do have to remind you latex is a sensitive material
so don't do this with sharp fingernails or don't poke it like with one finger all the time
because it can tear. But if you know how to handle your latex you should be fine.
Okay.
I can tell it was already slippery.
mother's always a lot of silicon oil or dressing aid helps a lot so use plenty
of that and yes of course you can dress latex also with talcum powder it's just
that I prefer silicon oil here okay next tricky part is getting the first arm in
by the way if you can see the stripes here it is from previous latex video and
and the latex was really tight so this happens but now like with the legs I'm
scrunching up the first arm making sure I know where the seam is where's the seam
here and then putting my arm through it
And then nice and slowly from hand to shoulder.
This is not on the right place.
Like this.
Yeah.
Okay, there is a lot of dressing aid inside.
sure there's no tension, not too much tension in one place. So distributing
tension evenly is also one of the keys. And now save for the second arm.
I don't know.
There's a lot of dressing aid inside. I can slosh around my arm like completely
because the seam wasn't on the inside but on the outside but it was no problem.
Wow. Okay.
Here we go. Done.
And I think it was way under 10 minutes so it's not like long.
but again it all comes with practice so that's how I got into it I hope
the question was answered this is how I do it
so of course this is also one of my cats so I know how to handle it and um yeah I don't know
just get the hang of it but for the next part getting out of it again and I don't know why
what a lot of people thought that it's harder to get out of than to get into it
why I'm going to prove you that it is way easier than getting into it all
right it's basically the same way again
My heart is always getting over the elbow I think.
There we go.
Arm number one.
Arm number two.
Done! You know when I answered questions in the comments under the last neck entry kits and video
I was asked how long do you need to get into it and out of it and I was like yeah into it maybe
10 minutes out of it, 1 to 2, there wasn't even one minute. Come on. Okay, now you demystified,
I guess, and know how to do it yourself if you ever want to get into a neck entry catsuit.
And I love neck entry 0.25 millimeter catsuits because they're just so comfortable,
because they're so stretchy. And you don't have an annoying zipper in the back or in the front
that doesn't stretch so yeah this is actually one of my preferred latex pieces good old catsuit
anyway that was it leave a comment if you have any pro tips or experiences I know you could have
used like an air pump to pump air into the catsuit so it settles a bit more into place or use the air
pump to deflate it or I heard some people do it under the shower with a lot of water if you ever
get stuck into your latex catsuit and want to get out of it go into the shower use water it's easier
but normally you either use enough dressing aid or sweat so much that it's always easy to get out of
anyway see you in the next video leave a thumbs up join my patreon have a nice day bye